Hello. And if you're in the same time
zone as us, good morning. You're
watching the program with Ted R and John
Kuryaku. It's Thursday, November 13,
2025. Thank you so much for joining us.
Good morning, John.
>> Good morning, Ted. How are you?
>> I'm okay. A little tired, but uh no no
good reason. Went to sleep at a
reasonable time. Just a little sleepy. I
don't know. It's it's the factor of fact
of getting old. Uh, it's not like I was
>> Go ahead.
>> I'm sorry to interrupt you.
>> Uh, it's one of these small world
stories. I'm in Oxford, Ohio visiting my
son and um, he asked me like a week ago,
do you know Muhammad Farag? And I said I
said, "Yeah,
he was the head of the Egyptian
intelligence service like 35 years ago.
I met him in Cairo and he said, "Well,
his son is my marketing professor and he
wants to meet you." And I said, 'I
remember him. He was a little kid when I
was there. He's like seven or eight
years old.
>> So, we all went out to dinner last night
and it it got late. That's why I'm so
beat.
>> Oh, well, at least you have a good
reason. You know, partying in Oxford,
Ohio could can go way past eight o'clock
at night, so it's get pretty crazy
there. Hunter Biden even couldn't handle
it. Um, [laughter]
at least I wasn't up all night reading
the Epstein documents, which I suspect
our president may have spent part of the
evening doing, although he's probably
already seen them all.
>> Yeah, he probably has. I I just figured
there were all kinds of people who were
already going to do that, so I wasn't
going to bother.
>> Yeah. No, that's that's that's the way I
look at it, too. Although sometimes, you
know, what amazes me is when there's a
huge data dump. Um, you know, it sounds
it's almost like it's worth going
through it yourself because stuff that I
find interesting is often left on the
cutting room floor uh when it ends up in
the New York Times or the New York Post
or wherever.
>> So,
>> that's exactly right.
>> All right. So, obviously we'll talk
about Epstein uh that Congress is uh in
fullfledged uh chaos over this. uh who's
to blame, who's the who are the real
perves, etc. Um over in Israel, worth
talking about is the is the violence in
the West Bank. Um the president Herzach
uh condemned it, I guess, better decades
late than never. Um and definitely the
lead topic that we put in the thumbnail
is just because I don't miss any chance
to use a sombrero uh in in in graphics.
uh Trump uh the Trump organization has
hired uh almost 600 foreign workers uh
at Mara Lago golf clubs, Virginia
estates um you know and so we got to
talk about that. uh you know is this a
reflection of the fact that it's
actually really hard to find American
workers and even someone like Donald
Trump whose politics go run counter to
this are like this or does he just do do
is this just another case of the rich
and powerful doing what they want and
they what they say to us is not
necessarily how they live their lives.
Um John what do you want to talk what do
you want to start with?
You know, I think we probably should
talk about the situation with the
Epstein files because it's becoming
unwieldy. It's it's it's spinning out of
control. So, we know thanks to these new
revelations that that Epstein and Galain
Maxwell were emailing each other back
and forth saying that that Trump knew
that these girls were underage. He never
did anything with any of them, but he
knew that this abuse was going on and
didn't speak out against it. Um,
that's very unfortunate, but it's not a
crime. As as awful as it is, it's not a
crime. They called Trump a scumbag,
which is no big deal either. My bottom
line here is this didn't make me love
Donald Trump anymore.
Um, I've never loved Donald Trump, but
this didn't change my mind. But it
wasn't, it didn't make things worse for
Trump. There's no they don't allege any
crime, even in their private, you know,
email communications.
So, here's here's the way things stand
in the House. The House does have the
218 votes for um the discharge petition.
It's out of Mike Johnson's hands. He has
to allow it to come to the floor because
they went over his head with the 218.
>> But that's not necessarily going to
change anything, Ted, because then the
Senate would have to to vote to release
the Epstein files, and then Donald Trump
would have to sign it, and he's not
going to sign anything that's going to
embarrass him or tarnish his his image
or his reputation. So this is all
another Washington tempest in a teapot
that nothing is going to come of.
>> So So basically what's come to be known,
correct me if I'm wrong about this, but
what's come to be known as the Epstein
files, there's really two batches,
right? So what has just come to light as
a result of the discharge petition is
what uh was under the control of the
House Oversight Committee. But that's
not the same ex it's not a duplicate set
of the documents currently being held by
the Department of Justice. Right.
>> No,
>> those documents.
>> That's correct. This is a different set.
>> So potentially
>> this is a different set.
>> So potentially there's other knowledge
either exculpatory or incriminating or
neither that are that are there. And
obviously Donald Trump's not like even
the primary target here. Uh I think
everyone sort of you know you end up
with a witch hunt in a situation like
this.
>> Um ethically yeah I mean you know it is
really interesting to put yourself in
that position and I kind of feel like we
all at some point I mean everybody
learns about lawb breakaking at some
point on the part of other people around
us whether it's co-workers or friends or
whatever and there's the question of
whether you should step forward and then
whether you could step forward. I mean,
let's just say for the sake of argument
that Trump decided he that he did know
about what Epstein was up to and he
wanted to do something about it. What
would he do really?
>> Yeah. What would he do?
>> I mean, who would he call?
>> I'm just not sure where this is taking.
>> We're not We don't live in East Germany.
I mean, you know, it's not like you can
call the Stazzi and they drag off the
pervert into the middle of the night.
Um, you know, nothing happens, right? I
mean, you know, you just yesterday you
mentioned a couple of cases where
someone called the cops and no one gave
a [__] And that's sort of normally what
happens, right? I mean, the cops are
It's like, well, I'm aware of a crime.
Okay, what evidence do you have? Well,
someone told me that's hearsay. We can't
we can't build a case on hearsay. Oh,
well, I have it on good authority. Okay,
we can't build a case on that either. I
don't blame the prosecutors. I don't
blame the cops. There's nothing really
that you can do in a situation like
that. I mean, I had a I drove a taxi in
the 80s and my one of my fellow taxi
drivers, you know, bragged about raping
a drunk woman in the backseat of his
cab. Okay, we all thought he was a turd
and we all hated him, but what could we
do? And he could have been making the
whole thing up. And what do we do? Call
the NYPD and say this guy raped, you
know, says that he raped a Okay. Well,
saying that you raped someone isn't a
crime. It just makes you a weirdass
liar. Um, so there there's just sort of
I mean, it's that whole I think people
there's an assumption there that if you
see something, say something will result
in something and I don't think that's a
valid assumption at all.
>> Yeah. I I have to agree. I have to
agree. It's the It's the society that we
live in now, you know. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, anyway, I I think nothing I
think nothing serious is going to come
of this uh Jeffrey Epstein thing. Now,
the Washington Post today has a piece um
in which they say that this is the only
issue that that seriously and solidly
divides Donald Trump from his base. It's
it remember it was it was the MAGA base
that was the first
political faction that we have in the
country to to shout for release of all
the documents. It was a campaign issue
and it's one of these issues that where
it was the street that dragged Trump to
the um to the the policy position.
>> That's the only reason why he ran on on
a a platform of releasing all of the
Epstein files.
and then he changed his mind and people
don't trust the reason for changing his
mind.
>> No, I mean I guess I mean look it's
entirely possible that his assessment is
simply like you know not I personally
didn't do anything but I was around bad
things that happened. It smears me. It
tarnishes me. It smears and tarnishes
people who I have a vested interest in
or who I used to be or am still
associated with. I mean, there's a lot I
mean, I think I think people have been
speculating about this in a very
simplistic way. Um, when it's anything
but simplistic. I mean, I can come up
with a a myriad of possible motivations
for Trump just preferring to put this
behind him. Not least of which is
politically, you're the president of the
United States. You have an ambitious
political agenda clearly whether you
agree with that agenda or not and you
don't want to spend the next three, six
months uh or whatever just talking about
this old [__] that you didn't have much
to do with but you know your old party
buddy was involved in.
>> Yeah, that's right. Um,
I want to thank Double D for the uh the
$4.99.
Double D says, "I hope people realize
that there will be foreign names on the
Epstein list. I think some Arab
higher-ups." There there are foreign
names on the Epstein list, and I think
there are probably going to be lots more
foreign names on the Epstein list as as
they continue to leak out. But we we've
known for a very long time that former
Israeli Prime Minister Ahoud Barack was
a regular visitor to Epstein Island. We
know from the release yesterday that
Barack's chief of staff was another one
who was a regular at the island and
there was there was some evidence
yesterday of of uh money being exchanged
too. So yeah, I agree with you. There
are there are foreign names on there. I
spoke with
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna break a little
news right now. So, I spoke yesterday
with a woman who used to be
the the chief of business development
for Giuliani Partners. She's suing Rudy
Giuliani for sexual assault. And she
told me that
she has thousands of pages of documents
that were
emails between Giuliani and Epstein, and
she's just waiting. She's offered them
up to different news organizations. She
offered them up to the investigating
committees on Capitol Hill. Nobody
cares.
And so she still has them. But she said
that there is another British prince
besides Prince Andrew who is implicated
who was also at the island and uh and
there are other um former heads of state
whose names have not been made public.
This is a a tough question and and John
I I won't be at all offended if you
don't answer it, but did you find her
credible? [snorts]
That's a good that's a good question.
Um,
>> you don't have to answer.
>> I find her Yeah. Yeah. No, no. I I I
find her credible in that I believe at
least I believe that she believes the
information is is correct,
>> right? She's very difficult to get along
with.
>> Um, and I think it's because she's been
traumatized.
>> Yeah,
>> that's Yeah, that's
>> She has tough
>> just crippling PTSD. It's sometimes
>> Yeah, she's she's very tough to carry on
a conversation with.
>> [snorts]
>> Um, [laughter]
>> there's a funny conversation in the chat
about whether or not we are gay. Um, I
had a I had a Yeah, I used to be I used
to have a a radio show in LA and we had
an open mic day and uh the one of the
questions that would always come up my
voice was higher then. It's not exactly
low and baritone but uh you know it was
always like is are you gay? And you
know, I never answered the question
because to deny it is to be like the
apostle who denies Christ, you know,
like before the before the [__] crows
three times, you know, it's like sort of
like saying that there's something wrong
with that to quote Seinfeld,
>> right? Not that there's anything wrong
with that.
>> No, no, not at all.
>> No, I'm not I'm not gay. Um I think my
two wives and five children would likely
confirm that. Uh, but I I don't care if
anybody's gay. It's none of my
>> I don't I I give no shits. Um, where
people put their junk. Uh, Mr. B.
Malarkey uh 9219 says that Drop Site
News is publishing all of it. I suspect
uh they're referring to the to all of
the Trump uh all of the uh all of the
Trump uh I mean all of the Epstein
files. I I don't know what we're talking
about here.
No, maybe maybe I should maybe I should
start uh
um reading Deadrop. I I've I've
boycotted them because they all came
from most of them came
>> or drop site, right? Drop site.
>> Uh
I I boycotted them because most of them
had come from the uh Intercept and I
just freaking hate I hated everybody at
the Intercept with what I think is very
good reason. Scale is not bad, I guess.
Grim is good.
>> Yeah. Scill skill is however the most
boring writer in the English language.
Um I I I tried to read his drone book
which you know I was obsessed with
drones.
>> Oh yeah.
>> And it was just like oh my god like dude
like it would be it would have been less
boring. I mean this was years and years
ago but if Chat GPT wrote the book it
would be a major improvement.
>> Yeah. But they do have some important,
you know, breaking news every every
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's I mean, it
their origin story is just very, you
know, flawed. The Pierre Odar influence
is toxic and
>> Yeah.
>> I don't understand. Oh, by the way,
John, I I have to thank you for sending
me that email that you got from the LA
Times. Oh my god,
>> how [__] funny is that?
>> I knew you'd like it.
>> Oh my god. So, so John, do you want to
describe it because you got the email or
I could do it, whatever.
>> Yeah. I got this automated email from
the LA Times yesterday saying, "Hey,
we're going to go public. Do you want to
get in early on on some insider shares?
Minimum investment is only $5,000 and it
entitles you to a 25% price discount
when we when we uh release our IPO." And
I was like, "Yeah, no. I'm not
interested in buying [laughter]
shares in a failing newspaper, but I
sent it to Ted. I thought he'd get a
kick out of it.
>> Well, not to mention it's so ghetto,
right? I mean, it's like I mean, so I
thought the whole point of a billionaire
buying a newspaper is that it doesn't
have to worry about money.
>> And so I guess if it's a fake
billionaire, um, then they do have to
worry about money even more. But Dr.
Patsun Xiang is like out like you know
with his tin cup uh you know be begging
for money from the likes of us and while
we're begging money for money from the
likes of you. By the way, please like,
follow, and share the show and and help
us uh and and help us like make a living
here. Um we do have some ads so I
probably should go go hit one. Uh well,
let's see. What should we do? What
should we do? Do we want to do we want
to do Catis Sports the cooler? We want
to do what do we want to do? Do we want
to do perplexity? That one seems to pay
well. Oh, Ivormectton. Oh, that that
>> I'm loving the perplexity people these
days. Let's do
>> Let's do that one. All right. Let's do
it. Here we go.
Oh, come on, Perplexity. Where are you?
Okay.
Okay. Looking for smarter ways to browse
and enjoy your favorite content without
ads? Get the Perplexity Pro bundle with
Rumble Premium for just $19.99 a month
when you sign up before December 31st.
Normally a $29.99 value. With Rumble
Premium, you'll get an ad-free viewing
experience across all your devices and
access to exclusive premium content. No
interruptions, just the video and
streams you love any anytime, anywhere.
Plus, Perplexity Pro boosts your
productivity with unlimited research,
unlimited uploads, exclusive member
perks, and access to the latest and most
advanced AI models for faster, smarter
answers every day. Save over 30% on this
powerful bundle. Head to
rumble.com/premium before December 31st
to sign up and unlock your premium
experience. Um, so speaking of premium
content, uh, John and I are going to be
recording a couple of premium Rumble
premium episodes. If you are not yet a
subscriber, um, you will be able to
unlock the, uh, life stories of John in
five parts, of me in four parts, uh, and
of Robbie in one part. Um, and also
we'll be talking, we're going to be
doing episodes about movies, books, um,
music, all sorts of stuff like that. So,
stuff that's a little bit off the beaten
path here for the regular show, a little
bit less serious, a little more relaxed,
letting your hair down. So, uh, you
know, you might want to check that out.
So, oh my god. But the LA Times thing
just cracking up. And by the way, if you
if you really want to burn through five
grand, better to give it to a homeless
person, you know? I mean, seriously,
because you're never going to see that
five grand again. I mean, LA Times is is
is doomed, you know.
>> You know, five five, six years ago,
seven years ago, I got one of those same
automated emails from Mercedes-Benz.
They had said that they were um I drive
a 14-year-old Mercedes-Benz, but they
said that they were um offering bonds uh
to all Mercedes-Benz owners and they
were going to use the money for XYZ
development of their new electronic car
or electric car system and uh it there
was a guaranteed return of like five and
a quarter% or something like that. So,
it was like very slightly better than
what you could get at the bank at the
time. That I would have done if I had
had an extra five grand that I didn't
care about. Um, but the LA Times, like
you said, the whole point of the
billionaire buying the Times is so that
he can save it. So, what now? We're
supposed to replace his money with our
own so that when it finally does go down
the drain, the billionaire gets to keep
his money and the little guy loses his
money.
That's precisely it fuse. Thank you fuso
for the buck. Uh, what's our favorite
Thanksgiving food? His or hers is
stuffing. John.
>> Yeah. You know what? I got to go with
stuffing, but it has to have gravy on
it.
>> U,
>> I go hot and cold on the turkey.
>> I despise Thanksgiving food. Um,
everything. Cranberry sauce, uh, turkey.
Hate it all. I'm an ultim guy. like give
me a ham, a steak, pasta, anything else.
But for traditional stuff, I got to go
with pumpkin pie. I I do like pumpkin
pie.
>> Ted, I was in college before I realized
that not everybody had like a table
covered in Greek food with the turkey in
the middle. [laughter]
>> I would have much preferred that.
>> I said, "That makes sense. We're the
ones that eat that have Thanksgiving
with all Greek food. Like I just It's
funny. When you're a little kid, it's
the normal thing. And all my life, I
grew up thinking that everybody just has
all Greek food with a turkey.
>> That is That's funny. I mean, I would
have God, I would have just
ignored the turkey and just just been
like, "Oh, yeah. G give me that Greek
salad. Um, you know, get me everything
else." Uh,
>> God, that's pretty funny. Um, all right.
Well, so all right. So, where does where
does the Epstein thing go from here
before we move on? I feel like right now
it's sort of like,
you know, it's it's sound and fury is
signifying very little. Um, am I wrong?
Uh, no, you're not wrong. Everybody was
looking for a smoking gun. They were
waiting for a smoking gun. This is not
the smoking gun.
One of the one of the commenters said in
the chat, "Two scumbags call another guy
a scumbag." Okay, big deal. It's It's
not It's not news. And the bottom line
is
even they are not accusing Trump of
having done anything with these girls.
Yes, he should have said something's
going on at this island. All these girls
are underage. Of course, he should have
said something, but he didn't do
anything to them.
>> But also, it's not new, right? I mean,
because there's the there's the pretty
uh well-known quote where Trump said
like, "Oh, you know, we have a lot in
common. We both really love beautiful
women, but uh you know, difference is
that uh you know, Jeffrey likes them
really really young." I mean,
>> come on. We know that he knew.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> When you hang out with a guy as much as
he did, you you know, you you know, you
gossip, you you know, I mean, Bill and
Hillary Clinton knew. Everybody knew.
They had to have known. And I guess the
question is to what extent is it
anybody's business? I mean, hell, he'd
already been prosecuted and let off the
hook by the authorities. And and that's,
you know, that's something that we
ignore here. I mean, I don't want to
sound like an apologist for the
president, but I've got to say, if I
were him, if anybody really put him on
the spot, he could say, "Listen, the
authorities had their chance and they
decided not to give a [__] What do you
want me as an individual private citizen
to do about it?
>> Exactly right. Exactly right.
>> I mean,
>> hey, um, if you don't mind, before we
move on to the next, uh,
>> there are a couple of things I wanted to
raise uh, from the papers today. So,
Reverend Jesse Jackson, everybody of
course [clears throat] remembers Jesse
Jackson. I never particularly cared for
him, [snorts] but um but he was
diagnosed back in 2015 with Parkinson's
disease and he said at the time that
that this was a disease that had failed
his father as well. It runs in families.
My dad had it. Um lots of my relatives
had it and um
he so he he was diagnosed with it in
2015. Two years ago, he was diagnosed
with something more severe, something
called supra nuclear paly, which is like
Parkinson's on steroids. And he was
hospitalized in Chicago yesterday. He's
84 years old. His prognosis is not good.
There's no cure for this. And you end up
if you don't fall and hit your head,
which is how my dad died, you end up
choking to death uh because you lose the
ability to swallow
>> or um or from pneumonia just because
your saliva collects in your lungs and
you you can't get relief from it. So I I
fear Jesse Jackson is uh not going to be
around very much longer. That was one
thing. The other thing, and it's less
important, but
>> by the way, it is important before we
let Jesse go. Um, you know, it's
important to comment on, you know, the
extent of his political achievement. Uh,
when he ran for president in ' 84 and
1988,
>> 88. That's right.
>> He carried a bunch of states in the
primary
>> as majority white states
>> as an insurgent black uh left-wing
progressive candidate. I would argue to
the left of Bernie Sanders.
>> I would
>> and and and like and and you know and an
an unapologetic
black politician uh preacher um you know
activist and you know like you I I kind
of am a little bit reserved about him
but I think there's no And by the way
full disclosure I did vote for him in
the primary in 1988. Um, so I I do, you
know, I mean you you gotta I mean and
also he was there like he's in that
famous photo of MLK dying on the
balcony. He's one of the guys. I mean he
was right there when he when he was
murdered. Kretta Scott King always
kept him at arms distance because that
day that MLK was assassinated with the
famous picture where everybody's
pointing at the room um as soon as he
was shot Jess Jesse Jackson was about 15
feet away from him when he was shot.
>> Yeah. When he was shot and he went down,
Jackson went over to him, [snorts] put
his hands in in Martin Luther King's
blood and then smeared the blood on his
shirt
>> to make it look like he had been like
right there when it happened. The next
day he went on Good Morning America and
he was still wearing the shirt.
>> Oh, so he was trying to be Jackie
Kennedy except she came about her uh
gristle honestly.
>> Yeah. and Ketta King never forgave him
for that.
>> If that's true, that's one of the most
disgusting things or and bizarre.
Fasmataz is asking if Jesse Jackson was
the FBI informant. Of course, uh you
know, obviously King was spied upon
ruthlessly by the FBI for many years. Um
is that I don't I don't know the answer
to that question.
>> I've read that it was not Jackson. It
was the older guy uh from the
from the Southern What was it called?
The Southern Baptist,
the Southern Christian Leadership,
whatever.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Conference.
>> Yeah.
>> Huh. Anyway. All right. Uh, by the way,
uh, this is so funny. I'm gonna put you
on the spot. This is mean and and you
know, we'll we can take him off if this
is a problem. But Elon Musk did arguably
more for humanity than even you. If you
don't like him, can you at least make
your best case for it?
>> For Elon Musk? No, I'm not going to make
it.
>> No, for for not I guess for not being
for for not for disliking Elon Musk.
>> Yeah, I think he's been bad for the
country. Nobody's worth a trillion
dollars. Nobody.
You can't possibly do anything
>> that is worth a trillion dollars. Yeah,
>> I mean he's a super interesting dude and
uh you know I can make the case for it
or against him, but I will say anybody
who designs a car that doesn't have
exterior door handles that allows the
firefighters to break you out in case
your car catches on fire is kind of like
missing a screw.
>> I know, right? That's true.
>> All right. Well, you had something else.
Oh. Oh, Al Sharpton. it according to USX
A-Rod was the in was an informant. Maybe
not the informant. I believe that. Oh
yeah. Yeah. Lisa Moika says Snick. Yeah.
The Southern What is it? The Southern
something. Oh god. Uh anyway,
>> leadership conference. Southern. Is that
right?
>> Something like that.
>> Oh my. Blake, thank you. Thank you for
$50. Here's some cash for tolerating my
annoying commentary. Obviously, you guys
aren't gay. [laughter]
Thank you. I was a conscientious
objector from the Army Infantry in 2009,
and John is my personal favorite
American hero. Thank you so much. You
are a conscientious objector. I read an
absolutely wonderful book, long out of
print. A a conscientious objector with
whom I I um was friendly. He's since
passed away. He sent me a book that was
published in like 1972,
maybe 1973 from, you know, his personal
collection. And it was it was just a
series of interviews with with
conscientious objectors. Some of them
had gone to Canada, others had been
arrested and imprisoned.
And the stories they told were were
harrowing. I think it was even in many
cases more dangerous, more physically,
personally dangerous for them to have
been a a conscientious objector and then
be sent to an American prison and not
not some clubfed like a a real honest to
god prison and then have to deal with
like I remember one one of the
interviews was a guy talking about
fending off um what they called in
prison the sisters. It was the the guys
who were situationally gay. They would
just rape the guys. Whatever new guy
happened to be in, they were either
gonna beat you to a pulp or they were
gonna rape you. One or the other.
>> Good times.
>> So, every day it was another fight for
this poor guy. So, being a conscientious
objector is a very brave thing to do.
>> I had a roommate uh not a roommate, a
classmate in uh at Colombia. Uh it was
1981 and uh DRA Carter had just started
draft registration and Reagan had just
become president. And like me, um, he
refused to sign, uh, to enlist to sign
up for draft registration. But unlike
me, they came and found him. And unlike
me, when they came and found him, uh, he
refused. So they sent him to federal
prison for five years. Um, and uh, that
that's the penalty still.
>> Um, and they take and they and they take
away your financial aid if you're in
college, too. Um, so I mean it's it's
and I was like and I was just like I was
impressed because there was no
publicity. Nobody cared. It was never in
the newspaper. And he and he didn't
care. It was just like I'm just not
signing. I'm just not doing it. I just I
won't. You can't make me and I'm not
gonna I think he also faced a $10,000
fine, too.
>> Wow.
>> Which was a lot of money at the time for
an 18-year-old kid.
>> Yeah, that's that's a lot of money. And
in those days,
>> psychonaut2, thank you for the dollar.
As an autistic guy, I see the flaws in
myself and Elon magnified into
billionaire level.
>> Yeah. Fo dollar. Uh, thank you for the
dollar. Did you discuss politics with
the mob in prison, John? Uh, what were
their what were their
>> politics? A lot.
I I had dinner with two with two of them
in uh in Philadelphia over the weekend.
Um,
they love love love Donald Trump. They
love him,
you know, and I think it's because being
a real estate developer in New York of
all places, you're going to have daily
contact with the mob. They control
everything. They control the, you know,
the concrete union, the union that makes
windows, the steel workers union. They
control everything. And you've got to
deal with these people if you want to
build buildings on your building.
>> That's why Trump had those connections.
He had to.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. So, um, yeah,
they love Trump. There's no two ways
about it.
>> Marvel 455. Thanks for the $4.99. Guys,
I didn't know this. The president of
Israel can pardon the prime minister
Netanyahu, but only if the request
letter came from the victim or their
family. That's a little bit reminiscent
of Sharia law where the victim or the
close relative of the victim can uh
either mitigate or forgive uh your uh
your sin, your crime.
>> Yes.
Yes. Exactly. And Trump, at first Trump
just asked the president of Israel. Now
he's actually written a formal letter
asking again the president of Israel to
uh to pardon Netanyahu. I think this is
something that he promised Netanyahu he
would do uh during uh during
>> but he doesn't have standing. Trump
doesn't have standing, right?
>> No, zero standing. Nothing. Nothing
standing.
>> They would have to be a victim of of
Netanyahu's corruption.
>> And and the Israeli people are the
victims of Netanyahu's corruption.
>> Right. So any Israeli taxpayer could
probably have standing.
>> I don't remember who I was talking to
earlier this week. It may have been on
my other podcast. we were talking about,
you know, in in the five or six weeks
before the October 7th attacks, um
Netanyahu's government was on the verge
of collapsing
and um there were people in the streets.
Remember, they even had to shut
Bengurian airport because there were
such massive demonstrations, you know,
people couldn't get to and from the
airport, they just shut it down. And
then October 7th happened and it unified
the whole country, at least briefly. And
uh Netanyahu is still around. I I have
been saying in podcasts that Netanyahu
has never ever received more than 27% of
the vote in any of his campaigns for
prime minister. He's the longest serving
prime minister in Israeli history. And
somebody challenged me that the other
day and said that's ridiculous. Israel
loves Netanyahu. I went back and looked
at it and I was wrong. It was not 27%.
It was 24.3%.
was the most Netanyahu has ever
received.
>> That's crazy.
>> So to be to to be anti-semitic if you
criticize Netanyahu is a red herring
>> that is being foisted at us.
>> Well then yeah at that rate the people
of Israel are all anti-semites. Uh $2
contribution from real real. Thank you.
Gentlemen, please share your thoughts on
Epstein helping to uh helping to sell
Israeli mass surveillance software to
the Ivory Coast in 2014.
>> He was much more than just an investment
banker. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I
>> I would say he was a financial fixer
would be the best way to describe
>> I would I would agree. I like that. Um,
and I would say I would reiterate my
earlier position that Netanyahu was an
access agent for the Mossad.
I mean, that's what it everything points
to that. Everything that he worked for
Mossad,
you know, I saw what's that idiot's
name? Um Andrew Bamante the other day on
some interview and he's looking right in
the camera and he's saying definitively
uh Jeffrey Epstein was uh working for
the FBI. He's clearly an FBI uh
informant, FBI agent. It's like you
don't even know what you're talking
about FBI. The FBI is not going to run a
pedophile against former presidents and
world leaders. The Israelis certainly
will.
>> The Israelis certainly will because then
you can get them in compromising
positions. You can use blackmail, which
we don't use, but the Israelis use. And
um and get them to give you information
on, you know, how the policy sausage is
made. They're all connected.
FBI.
John, while we're talking about Israel,
and I don't think this is worth a a
lengthy discussion, but uh it's is it
worth noting that uh the president of
Israel, who could uh as we noted, uh
forgive Netanyahu, um pardon Netanyahu,
uh he's coming out, he's you know, the
president of Israel is supposed to be
like the moral center. Yeah. Of the
nation
>> and and he he's not really powerful.
He's more of a figurehead. He's like,
you know, like kind of like the king of
Thailand, right? Yes. Um is has has a
role like that. Um and anyway, so
Herzach um stepped forward and and
condemned the settler colonists in the
West Bank for you know, running rampant
um you know, where they've been uh you
know, attacking Palestinians in their
own land and stealing their land and
trashing and vandalizing and and
committing arson and and rape and murder
too and robbery. uh you know basically
they're they they've been completely
operating with impunity. The IDF just
sort of stands stands by and smirks and
watches the whole thing either directly
with their arms crossed or from drones,
right? Like watching the whole thing.
They have drones everywhere on the West
Bank. Um I guess the question here is um
and finally there were a few arrests
that's like almost never happens. Um how
important is this? I mean, it seems like
uh the war in Gaza, the you know, the
the the world's attention is off that in
light of the sort of tentative
ceasefire. Um and now people are
starting to pay more attention to the
West Bank. But um the West Bank has been
a hot zone for years that no one was
paying attention to. I'm just like
trying to figure out the symbolism of
this. Does it resonate? It doesn't res
really resonate internationally, but
does it resonate domestically?
Yeah, I I would agree with that. Yeah, I
would agree with that. Hey, a couple of
other things, too, in the news. I I
meant to I meant to text this to you
last night. Did you happen to see this
announcement out of the State Department
that we're not going to allow fat people
to apply for immigrant visas anymore?
[laughter]
>> Yes. Or tourist visas, I think.
>> Or tourist visas. So, fat people can't
come to the United States. Period. and
immigrants.
>> No fatties allowed.
>> No fatties allowed into the fattest
country in the world. [laughter] And
>> so sad
>> today there was a report that No, it's
it's beyond that. So yes, no fatties are
allowed to apply for visas, but you're
not allowed to apply for an immigrant
visa now if you have cancer or diabetes.
>> Well, we did have a we did have a long
uh no AIDS policy for tourist visas,
right?
John, I had to I I was meaning to ask
you this question. So visas are
bilateral, aren't they?
>> Oh, yeah, they're bilateral.
>> So, doesn't that mean that like now
other countries have to ban fat
Americans?
>> Yeah, they they are. Um,
yeah, they they could absolutely do
that. Normally, what that means, the
agreement that we have with virtually
every other country in the world, it's
called the reciprocity agreement, the
visa reciprocity agreement. So normally
what it means is
we'll let the other country set the
price of the visa.
>> If the visa is free for Americans, then
our visas are going to be free for you
guys. Uh the Indians charge us a hundred
bucks. So we charge the Indians 100. The
Chileans charge us 100, we charge the
Chileans 100,
>> which made me so mad when I landed in
Chile.
>> Although sometimes they deny that. Uh
sometimes like other country like uh
when I went to Russia once the visa was
$400 and and the Russians said no no no
that's not us that's the Americans doing
that to us because the Americans were
trying to keep Russian mobsters from
coming to the US in the 90s.
>> Oh yeah $400 is going to deter them.
[laughter]
>> It's great
>> very poor mobsters. But but in this case
certainly any country can decide if the
Americans aren't gonna if the Americans
are going to make you get on a scale
when you go to the US embassy to apply
for a visa then we're going to make you
get on scale.
>> Yes. Absolutely.
>> So I mean that's I mean seriously that's
going to put a major crimp on tourism
and like nobody even knows what the
standards are. I think even if like even
if you're skinny I mean come on if I
mean I'm not the thinnest guy in the
world. Uh I've lost some weight lately.
I'm happy about it. But like, you know,
but seriously,
you know, why wouldn't everybody just
say, "Fuck you. [__] the United States.
Go [__] yourselves and your cheese curd
in Wisconsin and and your fat [__]
president who obviously doesn't own a
mirror." And like, [__] you guys. [__]
you all. I mean, isn't isn't that kind
of like that's what this is asking for?
>> It's coming. It's coming already. Spain
and France are coming right up to the
United States in the number of tourists
uh every year. And you know, every year
we're number one. Always. We're always
number one. And we're not going to be
number one anymore. Hey, I wanted to add
one other little micro news piece. Um I
saw this yesterday uh in one of the
local papers here in southern Ohio. I
didn't realize yesterday
the US Mint
um made the last penny.
>> The penny is no more.
>> It is no more.
>> Yep. as a former as a as a collector of
not just political buttons but also
coinage. Um I understand this um you
know coins I mean like for example uh I
remember when France went through this
um when they got rid of this when they
still had Franks and the Santine was you
know 1/100th of a frank a frank was
roughly uh 1/5if of a dollar and the one
Santine coin was literally so was worth
one of a US cent and it was cute little
tin coin um
>> and at a certain and I was kind of like
why do they still have these and of
course This was in the I believe in the
late 70s or early 80s France abolished
the Santine coin and the five Santine
coin became effectively the penny the
smallest and uh I don't know if five Sim
coins or five cent coins still even
exist in France they might be down to
the 10 euro cent coin um but it is it
does seem it's a sign of inflation right
I mean it costs 4 cents to make a penny
Um they're they're a pain. I I
understand the the case against them,
but you know, we've had coinage that
we've abolished over the years. There
used to be three cent coins uh in the in
the 19th century. Um yes, the $2 bill
comes and goes.
>> Uh you know, there was fractional
currency. I mean, I don't know. I mean,
>> how how resonant is the symbolism for
you?
>> Yeah. You know, actually the symbolism
is more important to me today than I
than I imagined it would be. I kind of
feel bad about the penny. It's been
around forever and now we I mean,
listen,
>> it also eliminates Abe Lincoln from our
coinage.
>> Yeah, it does. That it does. And this
new Trump coin that that the just that
the Treasury Department approved. Did
you see this? it. It's the first coin
ever by [snorts] the US Mint to have the
person's face on both sides
>> and to be of a living person.
>> Yeah. And to be of a living person.
>> I mean, it's a commemorative coin. It's
not like a a mass circulation coin, but
still.
>> Um, Soden 2324. Sorry we uh missed your
initial question. And we have two
questions in the feed. Thank you so much
for the 1999.
>> Um, thank you. What what are our
thoughts on Candace Owens and would you
appear on her show? And why am I warming
up to Marjorie Taylor Green? She might
get an invite in invite to Thanksgiving.
Well, I'm definitely warming up to
Marjorie Taylor Green as well.
>> I am too. I said that this week on
another podcast. I can't believe I'm
finding myself in in agreement with
Marjorie Taylor Green, you know, more
often than not.
>> Would you go on Candace Owens's show? I
would.
>> Um, six months ago, I would have said
absolutely not. And today I say
absolutely yes.
>> How come? Why? Why the difference?
>> I don't know. It's like she became sane
all of a sudden. Like overnight she
stopped talking about the lizard people
and the you know aliens and all this
stuff. And
I don't know.
>> I'll pretty much go on with anyone
especially if they have a decent sized
audience. um unless they prove
themselves to be like untrustworthy or
they're going to sandbag me or want to
talk about something that they said that
they didn't want to talk about or that I
didn't want to talk about.
>> I mean, generally, I just show up and
I'm willing to talk about anything,
>> but like for example, I won't go on with
Hannity because uh I was invited to go
talk about a controversial Gary Trudeau
cartoon and uh and then I was like,
"Okay, so this is about Gary Trudeau,
not about me." Yes, you're sure 100%.
And of course immediately when I got
there, he turned it against me. I was
ready because I know what a lying sack
of dung he is, but I'm not, you know,
I'm not but I mean I'll never go back
because it's just like, you know, that
kind of behavior can't be rewarded.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Um al uh so 2324 thank you additionally
for $9.99. Um John, will RFK be invited
to the Schllothbergs for Thanksgiving?
Wonder what that dinner conversation
will be about. Will it be cordial or
will the knives be out?
>> Sorry again for missing your first
question in the scroll here.
>> It's a little easier to to not miss
these once Robbie's back on Monday.
>> The the knives are already out. Jack
Schlober, the the grandson of uh
President John F. Kennedy uh announced
his candidacy for Congress yesterday in
the Upper East Side and upper west side
district currently represented by Jerry
Nadler. Jerry Nadler said, "I'm too old.
I'm in my 70s. It's time for a younger
generation." And he decided to retire.
So kudos to him. Schllothburg jumped in.
There are two or three other people
running like a city council member and
some state representative. Schlesber's
going to win that seat. Um
but he has come out very strongly
against his depending on how you look at
it first cousin once removed or or
second cousin RFK Jr. strongly against
him and um and I read yesterday it was
actually the family member that that
wrote the press release saying we
condemn RFK Jr.
So, uh, yeah, I think I think there's
going to be another Kennedy in Congress
next year. I read that that since 1946,
we've gone only two years without a
Kennedy in an elected or appointed
office.
>> Since 46. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, Phil 78 wants to know what we do
when we're not deprogramming,
deadropping, or writing. I guess asking
about hobbies like collecting. [snorts]
>> Well, I'll tell you, speaking of
collecting, my son and I day after
tomorrow are going to go to his favorite
antique gallery in uh Indianapolis.
Indianapolis isn't far, two, three hours
from here. So, we went last year and we
bought every bit of Lincoln memorabilia
we could find. There was one that I left
behind
and it was a hunk of wood from the
gallows where the conspirators were
hanged.
>> No way. That's so cool.
>> And
>> that's like a that's like a Jesus relic.
It's like a true cross.
>> And it had the provenance with it and it
had a what do you call it? An
authentication.
>> But it was $600 and I didn't want to
spend $600.
And I'm hoping I'm hoping it's still
there.
>> Sometimes I I I will leave a note with
someone and just say like, "Hey, you
know, no offense, I can't really afford
$600, but if you, you know, ever see
your way clear to maybe letting it go
for less. Please give me a call." By the
way, there's great there's a two really
great antique uh barn kind of places on
Interstate uh 70 uh near Springfield,
Ohio, not far at all from where you are.
>> No.
Um, fantastic. And also there's some
like there's a little I forget the name
of the town. It's not Cedarville, but
which is a great town, but there's a
town near you that has a lot of antique
um uh stores.
>> I'll check it out on 76
uh right outside of um of Akran.
There are a couple of really terrific
antique malls right Yeah. Right on 76.
>> Yeah, I've I've done that. That's on my
uh on my way on my That's on my way to
my college. Drop off and pick up also.
Totally. I know that drive very very
well. It's a bleak part of the state.
It's a bleak state.
>> Except for Cincinnati, which I love.
>> Gotta love corn.
>> Yeah, you do. So, what do we do? I mean,
well, I mean, I I like to bike and I
reading is number is my number one thing
as you know. I I I I I I'm read a lot of
non-fiction. [snorts]
>> Movies.
>> Yeah, I love movies.
>> I watch a lot of movies.
>> Yeah, movies and movies and uh and TV
and stuff like that.
>> Hey, and now did I did I tell you about
the letter I got from the Screen Actors
Guild?
>> Yeah, go ahead. Say that. Yeah, I don't
know if we did we talked about it here
or not. So, they sent me a letter saying
that they wanted to confirm my mailing
address because um they want to ship me
the box of all the DVDs of all the
Screen Actors Guild Award nominees so
that I can vote for the Screen Actors
Guild. Very exciting.
[laughter] I've never been able to do
something like that before.
>> Sen is claiming that we didn't really
answer his questions about Candace Owens
and stuff. I don't know. Yeah, I would I
would definitely go on Candace Owens.
Definitely. She's got a a a wide reach.
She's not as crazy as she used to be. Um
I still disagree with a lot of what she
has to say, but yeah, I would definitely
go on Candace.
>> And oh, and and in terms of the
Schllothbergs, I think, you know, I
don't know [laughter] if that can't
answer a question. I don't know the
answer to
>> Patrick Crabtree. Uh what gallery is it?
I live only an hour from Indie. I don't
know. And I'm going to find out. I'll
ask him the name.
>> Yeah, I'm having I'm having recall. It's
driving me crazy about the antique town
in Southwest Ohio, but it's like it's a
town where basically there's nothing but
antique stores. Um if you just
>> Oh, I would definitely do that.
>> Crack it. You'll find it. Um you kind of
have to choose the day of the right day
of the week. Like Saturday is probably
the day to go. Um but okay, so let's
talk about um these foreign workers. So
I have to say uh if we had Robbie here,
we'd pop him on. he'd go on a mad tear
about this. Yeah.
>> Um the Trump Organization
uh is ask requested 184 H2A and H2B
visas for Mara Lago, the golf the golf
clubs and the Virginia estates and so on
for farm hands, housekeepers, servers.
That's up from 121 in 2021. Total of 566
so far. He went on Fox and the president
went on Fox and just basically said he
can't find anyone any good anyone good
to work. MTG M Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar
Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar Mar
Mar Mar Mar Mar Marjorie Taylor Green
says this is [__] and it's wrong
>> and I agree with her on that. Um I mean
look if you pay people enough money you
know you can get them to do any job and
anybody who doubts that I will point out
the fact that you could hire Americans
to do asbestous removal. You can find
Americans to mine coal. You can find
Americans to process to work in nuclear
power plants. Okay? So, Americans will
do people Americans will work uh
collecting suck up carbon monoxide,
collecting tolls uh on highways.
Americans will do all sorts of [__] that
is very unpleasant, but you have to pay
them. And um and I I don't know. I mean
it's like is it is it really possible
>> when employers say you know it's like
with someone you have someone a friend
who says oh I can't sell my house I'm
like well you can't sell your house for
what you want for it I bet if you sold
it for 10 bucks you could sell your
house right so similarly when an
employer says I can't hire anyone well
you mean you can't hire anyone for what
you want to pay but mean that means
you're not really in the market you have
you're off the market um you need to hit
the market and if you can't afford to
pay people it means you can't really
afford to be in business or you can't
afford to hire these employees. I mean,
that's my take, but is but you know, is
I want to be fair. Is it possible that
really truly there's just there's really
no Americans to do these jobs and you
have to find foreigners when you go on a
cruise or you go stay at a resort in
Florida or anything like that.
Everybody's always from some foreign
country, right? They're always on one of
these like H2A visas. Um
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah. I mean, but I but but I mean, but
the hypocrisy here is really rank
considering that this is the most, you
know, anti-immigration president we've
ever had.
Yeah. But this is not new. This was an
issue in the 2016 presidential election
that he does this every year, not hiring
Americans, looking for cheaper foreign
uh workers. Every year the Trump
organization would would bring these
people. You know, when when I was
married, we used to go to um go to the
Outer Banks of North Carolina every
summer. We love it there. It's clean.
It's green. Beautiful.
We never encountered an American
lifeguard.
Uh we encountered almost no American
store clerks, shop clerks, waiters, and
waitresses. They were all from Bulgaria,
Romania, Moldiva,
all over Eastern Europe. And it's
because they work on the cheap in the
state and the working conditions blow,
right? Like like on a like on a ship,
they work ridiculous hours.
>> Yeah. And the And they're all living in
group houses. So you put eight or 10, 12
people to a house,
>> pay them the minimum wage, and then send
them back at the end of the season.
>> They're disposable. Yeah, I'm I'm I'm
I'm so against this. I mean, as long as
there's one undermployed or unemployed
American, this should just not be
permitted.
>> Agreed.
>> Um Agreed. You know, I mean, I don't it
it just makes no sense to me. Like, you
know, we have people who are literally I
mean, we have we have people who
graduated from, you know, from Harvard
Law who can't find a job. We have people
who went, you know, who went to MIT, uh,
who are like, "Oh, you're you're you're
coding you're you're 40. You're a coding
dinosaur." And they can't get a job. I
mean, it's outrageous. And I mean, I
guess I mean, but I guess um Trump's
base isn't going to hold him accountable
for this, right?
>> I don't know, man. They they let him get
away with so much as it is. I'm not I'm
not sure that they that they will let
him get away with it.
>> Phil is uh says, "Can we agree that
anti-immigration is actually
progressive? Importing unlimited
foreigners destroys culture, which I
think is more of a uh that's more of a
right-wing concern. Not that it
shouldn't be a left-wing concern, but I
think just it is destroys supply and
increases demand all while reducing
access to needs." Look, I agree with
that. I've been against this kind of
unfettered uh importing foreign workers
is is something I've been opposed to. I
mean, I'm on the record for favoring a
border wall back in the 1990s. So, yeah,
I agree.
>> Yeah.
>> Um Fo, thanks for the buck. Richard
Marines officers are American while the
crew are all Southeast Asians.
>> That's a good point, too.
Yeah, that's a good point, too. I mean,
although I do think we should have as
many fat tourists as want to come to the
[laughter] United States as possible. I
It's very [__] up. I mean, and and
seriously,
do you think Trump doesn't know that
he's overweight?
>> I think that he probably deep down
believes that he is overweight, but
thinks that nobody can notice. Nobody
has has picked up on it yet.
>> [laughter]
>> Like you never really you never really
realize how fat you are.
>> I really I mean
>> so
>> I totally think I'm fat as [__] I look
at the mirror I'm like oh my god what's
with this waddle?
>> This this is new just in the last like
12 months. I don't know where the hell
this came from
>> really. I don't even see anything. At
least you have a chin. I'm like I have
like Well, I have several to choose
from. [laughter]
>> Um yeah. Hey, before we before we leave,
>> I'm very proud to say that my cemetery
book is coming out on uh on March the
24th. It's called Remains of the Day, a
definitive guide to Washington DC's
[clears throat] historic cemeteries. If
you go to rarebirdlit.com,
um it's there for pre-order, but for
signed pre-orders,
rarebirdlit.com.
And uh I'm sitting in this hotel working
on book number nine, The Whispers from
the Grave, The Mafia Graves of New York
City.
>> So that'll be done soon, too.
>> Awesome. Um well, I think that's a good
place to end it. Uh I'll I'll put in
I'll do my pitch for my most recent
book, What's Left? Never mind the
Democrats. Go to rall.com and check that
out. Uh and I'll sign it for you uh if
you buy it through rall.com. Um, anyway,
please like, follow, and share the show.
We'll be back tomorrow at 9:00 am
Eastern time, and we're here every
Monday through Friday. Uh, please stay
tuned. We will be, uh, I I'll still be
on the air with Manila Chan for the TMI
show uh, coming up right at the top of
the hour at 10 o'clock Eastern. And, uh,
you'll just, if you're in the Rumble
room, you'll just be magically whisked
away there. And then I have three hours
of straight talk this morning. It's
Thursday, which means it's time for the
DMZ America podcast with Scott Stantis.
We'll be interviewing Salt Lake City uh
Tribune cartoonist Pat Bagley, who
actually fled the United States for
Portugal because of Donald Trump
becoming president of the United States.
So, John, see you tomorrow.
>> See you tomorrow.